web-dorado.com 2019-11-19

# Privacy Policy | Web-Dorado

Welcome to the WebDorado (hereinafter “Us”, “We”, “Our”, “Company”, “WebDorado” depending on context). Your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy applies to all Visitors and Users using or accessing WebDorado, including the Website found at (https://web-dorado.com), Plugins, Themes, and WebDorado Services and any other product or service that we may provide and maintain. The terms described in the Policy define how we collect, use, treat and safeguard your Personal information and the options for you to control your information. WebDorado is Armenia registered Company, with mailing address: Dorado Web LLC 2 Mayisi 9 st, apt 14 0039 Yerevan, Armenia 

### What data is collected

The information is collected when you visit and/or use WebDorado Products and Services (e.g. registration, subscribing to services, enrollment into affiliate program, placing a support ticket, communication with WebDorado, etc.). 

#### Registration and Account

A unique numeric ID is created and assigned to your account upon registration.

Action | Data collected | Is data stored | Retention Period  
---|---|---|---  
Free account creation | 

  * First Name
  * Last Name
  * Email Address
  * Password

| All data is stored in our Web-Dorado database | Personal data is retained until you request us to delete your personal data  
Login with Facebook | 

  * First Name
  * Last Name
  * Email Address
  * Facebook account id

| All data is stored in our Web-Dorado database | Personal data is retained until you request us to delete your personal data  
Creating an account and buying a product with credit card directly on web-dorado.com | 

  * First Name
  * Last Name
  * Email Address
  * Password
  * Credit Card Info (Name on card, Credit Card Number, Validity Date,CVC)

* In case of existing account only Credit Card info is collected

| All data is stored in our Web-Dorado database, except Credit Card Information, which is directly sent to PayPal to process your payments (Please see details in “Third Party” section). | Personal data is retained until you request us to delete your personal data. Please note, that requesting to delete (terminate) your account will not result in deletion of your personal data from payment information. If you want all your personal data to be deleted, you need to request us “Personal data deletion”  
Creating an account and buying a product using PayPal payment option | 

  * First Name
  * Last Name
  * Email Address
  * Password
  * PayPal Email Address

* In case of existing account only PayPal Email Address is collected

| All data is stored in our Web-Dorado database | Personal data is retained until you request us to delete your personal data. Please note, that requesting to delete (terminate) your account will not result in deletion of your personal data from payment information. If you want all your personal data to be deleted, you need to request us “Personal data deletion”  
Editing Account Information/User Profile | 

* Note: The additional (additional to data provided during any of above actions) information you supply here is optional. Optional data include

  * Phone Number
  * Your Time Zone
  * Company Name
  * Website
  * VAT Number (EU only)
  * Company Address
  * City
  * Country
  * Postal Code

| All the optional data is stored in our Web-Dorado database. | You can delete this information anytime from your account.  
Adding payment method | 

  * Credit Card Info (Name on card, Credit Card Number, Expiry Date,CVC)

| No data is stored on our end. Data is sent directly to PayPal to process your payments (Please see details in “Third Party” section). | Please inform us when you need your payment data to be deleted from PayPal.  
  
#### Subscriptions and Memberships

Action | Data collected | Is data stored | Retention Period  
---|---|---|---  
Affiliate Program Membership | 

  * Username
  * Password
  * Email Address
  * Company Name
  * Website Address
  * First Name
  * Last Name
  * Country
  * Payment Method
  * PayPal email
  * IP address
  * Street Address (optional)
  * City (optional)
  * State/Province (optional)
  * Phone Number (optional)
  * Zip Code (optional)

| All data is stored in our Web-Dorado database | Personal data is retained until you request us to delete your personal data  
  
#### Other

Action | Data collected | Is data stored | Retention Period  
---|---|---|---  
Using Our Free Products from WordPress.org Repository | 

Note: all data is optional. You can opt to not provide below data.

  * Name
  * Email address
  * Website URL

| If you choose to provide requested data, it is stored in our Web-Dorado database. If you choose to skip, data is not stored. | Personal data is deleted in a month after you fully unsubscribe from our email communications  
Deactivation log | 

Note: all data is optional. You can opt to not provide below data.

  * Email address
  * Website URL

| If you choose to provide requested data, it is stored in our Web-Dorado database. If you choose to skip, data is not stored. | Personal data is retained for one month  
“Contact Us” form | 

  * First Name
  * Last Name
  * Email
  * Message Subject and Body Texts
  * Attachments

| All data is saved in Web-Dorado database and G Suite (Please see details in “Third Party” section). | Personal data is retained until you request us to delete your personal data  
Using Image Optimizer Service | 

  * Site and pages’ URLs
  * Site IP
  * Images

| All data is stored in our Web-Dorado database/ Cloud storage (Please see Third Parties for details). | Personal data is retained until you request us to delete your personal data. Images are cached for 72 hours.  
Support request through direct email. | 

  * Email Address
  * Message Subject and body texts
  * Attachments

| We are using G Suite and our proprietary Customer Care system. All data is saved in Web-Dorado database and G Suite (Please see Third Parties for details). | Personal data is retained until you request us to delete your personal data  
Onsite support temporary access (admin, FTP) to your website | 

Note* Provision of access is at your discretion.

  * Website link
  * Username 
  * Password

| The data (URL, Username, Password) remains in email communication between You and Us. | Personal data is retained until you request us to delete your personal data. We strongly recommend to disable access, once the support action is completed  
Publishing Content (blog post, replies/comments) | 

  * Name
  * Email
  * Website (optional)

| All data is stored in our Web-Dorado database | Personal data is retained until you request us to delete your personal data  
  
#### Third-Party Data Exchange

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal information. This does not include parties who assist us in conducting our business, or serving our users. We try to work with such parties, that adhere to the highest levels of privacy and security practices. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety.

Third Party | Data we provide to Third Parties | Data we get back from Third Parties | Data stored on our end and for how long | Links to third party Privacy Policy  
---|---|---|---|---  
Paypal | 

  * User ID
  * Credit Card Info (Name on card, Credit Card Number, Validity Date,CVC)

| 

  * Name
  * PayPal email address
  * Country

| All data is stored in our Web-Dorado database. All data is retained until you request us to delete your personal data | [Paypal](https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full)  
Google Analytics | 

Google Analytics collects

  * Anonymized IP address
  * Visitor behaviour

| Reports that do not contain personal data | N/A | [Google](https://policies.google.com/privacy)  
G Suite | We use Google/G Suite to process all internal email and communication with our customers. Your email address, and any data provided during the communication are stored in G Suite archives. | [Google](https://policies.google.com/privacy)  
Servers | All web servers and hosting are managed by our team on Google Cloud, AWS, OVH services. This includes website hosting, backups, web database, file storage, APIs, and log files. Our servers are in EU and/or in locations subject to Adequacy Decision and/or EU-US privacy Shield | [Google](https://policies.google.com/privacy)  
  
#### Embedded Services

Embeds are pieces from other websites content embedded on our website. They behave as if the visitor has visited their website and may use cookies or capture information. These services may collect your IP Address, store cookies on your browser, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content and such. Please see below the link to privacy policies of such embeds on our Website: [YouTube ](https://policies.google.com/privacy)

#### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Cookies and similar technologies (e.g. Local Storage) allow us to authenticate you, to track your browsing behavior, links clicked, items purchased, your device type, about how you use and interact with us and/or to run our Affiliate Program. This allows us to provide you with more relevant product offerings and advertisement, a better experience with our products and services, and to collect, analyze and improve our performance. We may also collect IP address to enhance security. Note that cookies may be placed by Third Party Services that we use (e.g. Google Analytics). You can choose to turn off all cookies at any time from your browser settings. If you turn cookies off, some features will be disabled such as not being able to log in to your account.

### Why we Collect Your Information?

All information collected by WebDorado is used for internal purposes of running the business, except the cases described earlier. We collect information mainly:

  * To be able to provide services
  * To form reports for provided services
  * To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of services and product offerings in which you are most interested.
  * To improve our services in order to better serve you.
  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or similar.
  * To quickly process your transactions.
  * Inform you on changes that may affect you
  * To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.

### Information Protection

We respect and are committed to safeguard your privacy and have undertaken and put in place some physical, electronic and managerial measures which will allow us to deliver on our commitments. Additionally, we try to work with such parties, that adhere to the highest levels of privacy and security practices. Our systems are scanned on a regular basis for security gaps and known vulnerabilities in order to make your usage experience as safe as possible. Your sensitive information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons and third parties who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to follow policies stipulated herein. All information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. We implement a variety of security measures when you place an order, enter, submit, or access your information to maintain the safety of your sensitive information. You also have a role in protecting your privacy. In particular, 

  * please keep your passwords in a safe place and do not share with others. If you have identified unauthorized use of your account or other security issues, please contact us
  * In case of onsite support temporary Admin, FTP access to your website, we strongly recommend to disable access, once the support action is completed. We will not use Admin, FTP access provided by you, for any other purpose, except the purpose we have asked access for and without your explicit permission. 

Nevertheless, you should know that electronic transmission and data storage methods are not perfect by their nature and thus, we cannot guarantee absolute safeguard for your personal information. We use third party servers to store your information. We run a thorough selection process to identify third party data storage providers, which utilize industry standard security mechanisms.

### Third Party Links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include third party links on our website. This may include different social media (Facebook, Twitter, Google+, Youtube, etc.) features, widgets. These third party sites/services have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Communications

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials, your subscription expiration, customer support issues and important updates. You may opt to not receive marketing/promotional communications at any time, by unsubscribing from those. In this case you will miss important information on WebDorado, its products and services. Please note, that you will still receive the type of communication from WebDorado, that we deem is necessary for continuity of WebDorado business and operations and maintaining the high level of security standards. Communicating with WebDorado may involve, but is not limited to, an exchange of information, discussions and information sharing, including, through publicly accessible platforms, such as WordPress.org support forum. You acknowledge your awareness that the information provided and/or posted by you on publicly accessible platforms may be accessed by any third party, collected, and used or misused. You take full responsibility of and agree to indemnify and hold WebDorado and its affiliate companies, and their officers, agents, employees, partners, and licensees harmless from any claim or demand arisen in the result of you posting sensitive information on abovementioned platforms. Additionally you acknowledge that during the communications you might submit, share, suggest, propose or make available to the company in any other way ideas pertaining to our product/service improvement and/or developing new product/service/functionality. Please note that many of the outside ideas submitted to the company may be already known or available to it and we do not offer compensation for ideas regardless of being known/available to us or being new and when the company at any time elects to practice them. We deem all ideas are gratuitously being made available to the Company, no consideration is expected and by using our services you consent to these terms. You agree to release us (and our officers, directors, agents, subsidiaries, joint ventures and employees) from claims and demands of every kind and nature, known and unknown, arising out of or in any way connected with your ideas made available to the company. You also consent not to exercise the moral rights of authors against the Company. Please consider these terms and conditions, before making an idea available to the the company. 

### Your Rights Over Your Data

We honor your right to be informed on and have access to your data that you provided to Us, as well as your right to request Us to delete your personal data.

To this end:

  * We take a great care to ensure the security of the personal data You have shared with Us (see “Information Protection” section),
  * Try to minimize the personal data we collect,
  * Inform you on what personal data is collected and ask for your consent to do so
  * Whenever possible, provide you with an option to choose to not provide Us your data
  * Option to change and update you personal data, whenever possible
  * We have put in place mechanisms and solutions, to export and provide you with your personal data we retain, upon your request
  * We have put in place mechanisms and solutions, to delete your personal data we retain, upon your request

You can reach us at [[email protected]](https://web-dorado.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#f685838686998482b6819394db929984979299d895999b) for requests related to our above commitments. We may ask to confirm your requests by sending an email to your email account registered with Us.

### What Data Breach Procedures We Have In Place

We take commercially reasonable measures to secure and protect your information transmitted via or stored in our databases. However, no security system is perfect. We cannot totally guarantee that information you supply to us will not be breached. Should a breach occur or potentially compromised, we will inform you via email within 72 hours of Us becoming aware of the event. We will also report such incident to any required data protection authority. We will work closely with affected users, to determine steps necessary to undertake and how to avoid any similar event in the future. 

### California Online Privacy Protection Act

CalOPPA requires commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates online services collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. - [See more](https://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/codes_displayText.xhtml?lawCode=BPC&division=8.&title=&part=&chapter=22.&article=)

#### According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:

Users can visit our website anonymously. Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website. Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can easily be found on the page specified above. Users will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes on our Privacy Policy Page. Users can change their personal information by logging into their account. 

#### How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?

We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

### COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States' consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online. We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.

### CAN SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them.

#### To be in accordance with CAN SPAM, we agree to the following

  * Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.
  * Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
  * Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
  * Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
  * Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

### Changes To This Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and it is User’s responsibility to check this Privacy Policy periodically. User’s continued use of our services after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute User’s acknowledgment of the modifications and consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we, at our sole discretion, may notify user either through the email address they have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website. 

### CONTACT US

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please [contact us.](https://web-dorado.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#0d7e787d7d627f794d7a686f2069627f6c6962236e6260)
